的确是段潮起潮落的人生路
So it has been quite a journey,
但自始至终 支持我走下去最大动力是勇气
but through it all, the key for me has been bravery
以及在内心深处我坚信
and the deep-down knowledge
我比所有人都强
that I am better than everyone else.
抱歉 吉利安 你的问题是什么来着
Uh, I'm sorry, Jillian, what was your question?
我问麦克斯是在哪里出生的
I asked Max where she was born.
90号洲际公路的躲猫猫酒吧
The Peekaboo Lounge on I-90.
我妈在舞台的钢管上时
My mom was on the pole
我从她下面跑出来 然后说"找到你啦"
when I popped out and said, "Peekaboo."
你的电影《庞氏公主》
So your movie, The Princess and the Ponzi,
有获奥斯卡的希望呢
has Oscar buzz...
虽然是最佳音效剪辑 但还是很棒啊
for sound editing, but still.
你们打算穿谁家的礼服去首映会呢
Who will you be wearing to the premiere?
吉利安 我的上衣来自
Well, Jillian, the top is from
便利商店的失物招领处
the 7-Eleven lost and found,
牛仔裤是我跟人拿刀对砍的战利品
and the jeans I won in a knife fight,
所以我也不知道是谁家的
so I didn't get specifics.
明星造型师布莱德·格雷斯基找我了
Stylist to the stars Brad Goreski reached out.
他是个时尚警察
He's a fashion policeman,
这是唯一一种还未逮捕过麦克斯的警察呢
the only kind of policeman Max hasn't been arrested by.
我们甜品酒吧将会承办首映会的餐饮
Anyway, our dessert bar is catering the premiere.
我们真的是越来越能自食其力了
We are really coming into our own.
姑娘们
Girls...
说到慢慢长大[自食其果]
Oh, speaking of coming into your own,
这位是阿憨
this is Han.
你们俩今天有打算来上班吗
Are you coming to work today?
还是我该自己来 直接写错客人的点餐就好
Or should I just write down wrong orders for customers myself?
阿憨 你看不见我们正在
Han, can't you see we're in the middle
接受我大电影的新闻采访吗
of a press interview for my movie?
别无视我啊
You can't just ignore me.
我又不是你们法院指派律师给的建议
I'm not the advice of your court-appointed lawyer.
听起来你们有很多事情忙
Sounds like you guys are busy.
宣传这部电影 经营这间酒吧
The movie, running this bar,
还要给那个男人打工
and working for that man too.
是男人 对吧
Man, right?
我们事业越来越蒸蒸日上
With us blowing up as we are,
我跟麦克斯也会慢慢挥别餐厅
Max and I are phasing out the diner
以及摸起来会烫的体香剂
and deodorant that's hot to the touch.
它能把臭味都烧掉 我才不要挥别它
It burns the stink away. I'm not giving that up.
很高兴聊了...五个小时
Well, that was...five hours.
首映会上见
Uh, see you at the premiere.
等等 我们要挥别餐厅吗
Wait, we're phasing out the diner?
看来我以后真的不可以你一开口
I have really gotta stop falling asleep immediately
就秒睡了
whenever you speak.
麦克斯 你自己想想嘛 为啥...
Max, think about it. Why--
阿憨 我们需要跟你谈谈
Han, we need to talk to you.
是的 跟你说话我们也很郁闷
Yeah, we're not happy about it either.
毕竟最好的情况
Best-case scenario,
是本可以今天一天都不见到你
we wouldn't have seen you at all today.
棒呆了 谈话呢
Oh, good, a talk.
我帮你们省点功夫 直接开始哭吧
Let me save you the trouble and just start crying.
阿憨 我们要慢慢将餐厅从我们生活中挥别
Han, we are phasing the diner out of our lives.
我现在是有造型师的人了
I have a stylist now.
这是我们的提前两周离职通知
This is our two weeks' notice,
我们这周还需要请假来准备参加首映会
and we need this week off to get ready for the premiere.
我说过我有造型师了对吧
I mentioned I have a stylist, right?
所以就这么抛下我[嗨干]吗
So you leave me high and dry?
在你身边我永远都又嗨又"干"
I'm always high and dry around you.
阿憨 我们请了鲍比的姐姐来代班
Han, we got Bobby's sister, Denise, to cover for us,
而且她已经迟到了
and she's already late.
跟我们在时一模一样吧
It'll be like we never left.
一身大汗还迟到 真是抱歉
Whoo, sorry I'm sweaty and late.
我试了用跑酷的方式赶来这里
I tried to parkour my way here.
然后我跟停车收费器亲密接触了
Then I met the business end of a parking meter.
简单来说就是撞坏了我的"洞洞"
Basically, I broke my vagina.
我能去哪里弄到一大袋冰块呢
Where can I get a big Ziploc bag full of ice?
我这有
Uh...here.
我本来用它来保存我的肾
I was keeping my kidney in it.
鲍比 在明星造型师
Now, Bobby, before stylist to the stars
布莱德·格雷斯基到之前
Brad Goreski gets here,
我们需要下点功夫
we just need to do a little work
改善一下你的服装 发型 脸蛋
to fix up your clothes, your hair, your face.
你走路姿势也不行
Also, your walk's not great.
那我跑步姿势如何
How's my run?
因为我现在就挺想跑的
'Cause I feel like doing it right now.
如果你想当造型师 就去帮帮丹妮斯
If you want to play stylist, help Denise.
她会把毛衣紮进...
She tucks her sweater in--
袜子里
to her socks.
丹妮斯并没有获邀去参加首映会
Oh, Denise isn't invited to the premiere.
我不想冒搬石头砸自己脚的风险
I can't run the risk of being embarrassed by someone.
厄尔已经问过我可不可以带
I mean, Earl already asked if he could bring
他的睡袋还有购物手推车来了
his sleeping bag and his shopping cart.
够了 厄尔 我们知道你有钱
We get it, Earl, you're rich.
我的礼服出自设计师创·丹
Uh, my dress is by Beddy Spready.
就是床单的意思
It's a bedspread.
天啊 布莱德·格雷斯基
Oh, my God, Brad Goreski!
我无法证明我是
Well, I can't prove it,
因为我刚在外面被人偷了钱包
because someone just stole my wallet outside.
好啦 我去搞套西装
All right, I gotta go get a suit
不过得先...
after I get my...
刷睫毛吗 你不是吧
eyelashes highlighted? Seriously?
爱你啦
Love you.
我也爱你
Love you too.
睫毛的事很正确
Good call on the eyelashes.
这公寓里第一次有比我更强的胸[衣架]
First time there's been a better rack than mine in the apartment.
这些是你们的候选礼服
Okay, these are the choices.
都是从顶级设计师那里借的
They're on loan from the top designers,
如果弄坏了衣服
and if you hurt them,
那些疯婆子会追杀你到天涯海角
those bitches will hunt you down.
如果连《美国警察》汤米·李·琼斯
Well, if Federal Marshal Tommy Lee Jones
都找不到我 她们就算了吧
couldn't find me, good luck.
这件是设计师扎克·珀森的新作
That's a brand-new Zac Posen.
他是帮忙我才借给我的
He gave it to me as a favor,
我们共同分享分时房产和对雪儿的爱
because we share a time share and a love of Cher.
分享过度了吗
Over share?
你那边有礼服是
You got anything over there
我不需要刮腋毛就能穿的吗
I won't have to shave my pits for?
你等等
Hmm, hold on.
我找一下
Let me sniff around
谢琳·伍德蕾参加演员工会奖穿的那条裙子
for Shailene Woodley's SAG Awards dress.
天啊 我好喜欢这条
Oh, my God, I love it.
眼光真好
Oh, good eye.
这条裙子价值一万美元
That's a $10,000 dress.
这就是为什么它在这间公寓里
And that's why it looks so lost
看起来是如此迷茫与害怕
and afraid in this apartment.
这价钱够我开一家平价服饰店了
I can own and operate an Old Navy for that.
天啊
Oh, my God.
有人打了时尚报警专线吗
Did someone call fashion 911?
时尚警察在这里呢
The fashion police are here!
被认出来好尴尬
Well, this is embarrassing.
是啦 我就是明星造型师布莱德·格雷斯基
Yes, I'm celebrity stylist Brad Goreski.
抱歉 我还以为你是女主持梅丽莎
Oh, see, I thought you were Melissa Rivers.
你们两个的下巴很像
Yeah, 'cause you guys have very similar jaws.
你帮婴儿做造型吗
Hey, do you style babies?
我想让芭芭拉在首映会
'Cause I want Barbara to be discovered
被人发掘
at the movie premiere.
我唯一帮做造型的婴儿是坎耶·韦斯特
The only baby I style is Kanye West.
等等 你真的不是梅丽莎·里弗斯吗
Wait, are you sure you're not Melissa Rivers?
麦克斯 这是我再度回归上流社会
Max, this is my reintroduction into high society,
你非得带着肋排上豪车吗
and you had to bring ribs for the limo?
某人明显没拍过嘻哈斗牛梗的音乐录影带
Somebody obviously was never in a Pitbull video.
这车感觉还得堵好一段时间
Doesn't look like we're going anywhere in this traffic.
给我来根肋排
I'll take a road rib.
麦克斯 你敢把红酒拿靠近我身边
Max, if you get that red wine near me,
我就开始唱音乐剧《滑稽女郎》的歌
I will start singing songs from Funny Girl,
而且绝对不停下
and I will not stop.
能给我来点"喝了才能忍卡洛琳"果汁吗
Can I some of that "Deal with Caroline" juice?
麦克斯 这是你第三声叹气了
Max, that's your third sigh.
是我的妆不够完美吗
Is my makeup not perfect?
就连我叹的气都得跟你有关吗
Do even my sighs have to be about you?
毕竟今晚我是主角嘛
Well, it is my night.
我只是在想这整件电影的事
I was just thinking how this whole movie thing
都起源于去洛杉矶见兰迪
started in L.A. with Randy.
有点难过他不在这里
It's kind of sad he's not here,
另外 你的妆有点小丑感
and also, your makeup is a little clowny.
不是吧
Oh, no.
好吧 兰迪是唯一一个
Yeah, well, Randy's the only person
我爱过 也接受他的爱的人
I've ever loved or let love me.
是有多小丑感
How clowny?
你们在这里干嘛
What are you guys doing out there?
太堵了 我们就下了出租车
We hopped out of our cab, because of the traffic.
还有就是那车着火了
Also, it was on fire.
我们也很想邀请你们上车
Well, we'd invite you guys in here,
但这车窗不停地自己关上了
but the windows keep going up on their own.
你觉得那个豪车司机
You don't think that limo driver's
应该不会把我剩下的卷心菜沙拉都吃完吧
gonna eat the rest of my coleslaw, do you?
没人走红毯时说"卷心菜沙拉"
Shh, no one says "coleslaw" on a red carpet.
我觉得你藏在杯座里藏得很妙
I think you hid it pretty well in the cup holders.
天啊 看看这里
Oh, my God. Look at all this.
太好了 卡洛琳·钱宁
Oh, good, Caroline Channing.
乖乖待着 还没到你
Stay here. It's not your time yet.
我把一台自动倾卸卡车
Oh, that's what the angels said to me
开进河里时 天使们也说了这话
when I drove that dump truck into the East River.
快看 《快乐的大脚》的演员
Oh, look, it's the star of Happy Feet.
南极在那个方向
Antarctica's that way.
放屁 是那边
No, it's that way.
好令人兴奋啊
This is exciting.
我上一次见到那么多狗仔队
I haven't seen this much paparazzi
还是在我跟哈莉特·塔布曼交往那会儿
since I was dating Harriet Tubman.
你们是许愿基金会的人[伴侣]吧
You guys must be the Make-A-Wish couple.
其实我们只是朋友而已
Actually, we're just friends.
如果我能许愿 我希望他是一根大号大麻烟
If I had a wish, he'd be a giant doobie.
继续往前走
Just keep it moving.
这里是给不红明星的位子
It's the "Kevin Dillon and below" spot.
他们肯定全部在换新胶卷呢
They must all be reloading their cameras.
所以你是说我现在
Are you trying to say I shouldn't be seeing
眼前不应该看到那么多闪光吗
all these flashing lights right now?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
看看我的红毯礼服
Check out my red carpet dress.
我跟你说"红毯服饰"时
So, when I said "Red carpet attire,"
指的是...
I meant something--wow.
出门前 我亲自把这块地毯吸了一遍
I vacuumed it myself before we left.
让我变成了"硬"木地板
It gave me hard wood.
今晚真正的大明星来了
Well, the real star tonight is here.
凡尔纳·泰勒吗 在哪里
Verne Troyer, where?
不是 是芭芭拉
No, Barbara.
来吧 芭芭拉 来把你变成巨星
Come on, Barbara, let's make you a star.
看 是波兰熏肠 你的最爱
Look, it's kielbasa, your favorite.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
这位是芭芭拉宝宝
It's baby Barbara.
这是大头照
Here are some headshots.
她长得又萌 又多才多艺
She's cute, she's versatile,
像她妈妈 她也能把十根脚趾都放进嘴里
and like her mother, she can put all ten toes in her mouth.
你在这里啊
There you are.
稍等一下
Oh, let's hold off a minute.
好莱坞金律 别跟着香肠[男人]
Old Hollywood rule: never follow sausage.
-谁下一个 -我来
- Okay, who's next? - Oh, I'll go.
跟着"香肠"是我的专利
Following sausage is kinda my thing.
天大地大有沟最大 有沟怎么玩都行
Doesn't matter what you do if you're rocking the cleavage.
谢谢你借他西装
Thanks for lending him clothes.
我让他买套酷一点的
I told him to get something cool,
结果他居然买了套短袖西装
so he bought a short-sleeved suit.
那可是来自动作影星斯蒂芬·西格尔夏季服饰系列
Yeah, it's part of the Steven Seagal summer collection.
我们准备好了吗
Hey, are we ready?
好了
Yeah.
你好帅啊
You look so handsome.
让我再弄一下你头发
Let me just fix that hair.
它又是我讨厌的那样子了
It's still doing that thing that I hate.
等等 貌似是你头型的问题
Actually, it might just be the shape of your head.
你在我前面一点走
Walk a little in front of me.
我想跟你一起分享此刻
I want to share this moment with you,
但我想一个人走红毯
but I want to do it alone.
-好了 -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
等等 等等 鲍比
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Bobby.
-不 鲍比 别走了 -我走着呢 走着呢
- No, Bobby--Bobby, wait! - I'm going, I'm going.
带着我奇怪的头型火速离开红毯
I'm moving as fast as my big misshapen head'll go.
卡洛琳 你要被拆开了
Caroline, you're unraveling!
鲍比 快回来
Bobby, come back!
鲍比 别走 我是说真的
Oh, Bobby, no, I'm serious!
我真不敢相信居然发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening!
而鲍比那里的头发还是往外翘
And Bobby's hair is still sticking up!
额滴神啊 这场面比
Oh, my God, this is worse than
艾瑞克·斯通斯崔特露奶还不堪
Eric Stonestreet's nip slip.
麦克斯
Max...
兰迪
Randy.
麦克斯
Max.
我...非常想留下来跟你聊聊
I'd... love to stay and talk,
可我刚想起来我得赶紧跑
but I just remembered I have to run away.
布莱德 帮帮忙呗
Brad, a little help?
你自己收拾这个烂摊子吧
You're on your own.
跟个白痴一样出现在首映会
Stupid showing up at movies,
一副"惊喜吧 麦克斯 我也在"
like, "Oh, surprise, Max, I'm here."
不好意思 我们不营业
Sorry, we're closed.
你刚才跑太快了
You ran out of there so fast,
踩到了那只奇怪的外国鸟
you trampled that strange exotic bird.
那是蒂尔达·斯文顿 而且我也道歉了
That was Tilda Swinton, and I apologized.
你怎么知道我在这里
How did you know I was here?
我跟踪[粉]你了
I followed you.
你可以在脸书上戳我一下告诉我啊
You could've just poked me on Facebook.
我更想亲自"戳"你一下
Rather poke you in person.
你要给我来杯喝的吗
So...you gonna give me a drink?
你要告诉我你为什么来这里吗
Are you gonna give me a reason you're here?
你要告诉我你为什么这么美丽动人吗
Are you gonna give me a reason you're so beautiful?
你要告诉我你为什么...
Are you gonna give me a reason--
算了 我给你倒一杯就是了
okay, fine, I'll give you a drink.
我好不容易忘了你
I just got over you.
你还想要我怎么样
What do you want from me?
我想跟你在一起
I want to be with you.
得了吧
Oh, please!
你觉得西装革履地出现在这里
You think you can just come in here in your suit
说一句"我想跟你在一起 麦克斯"就行了吗
and be like, "Uh, I wanna be with you, Max."
你还说你爱我
You say you love me,
说你没有我活不下去
you say you can't live without me,
结果呢 没有我你还是活得好好的
and then you go and live without me.
先生 你满嘴跑火车
You, sir, are unreliable.
麦克斯 我想你
Max, I miss you.
每次看见手指残留的奇多芝士粉
Every time I see Cheeto dust
或看见在高级餐厅里穿夹脚拖的女生
or a girl wearing flip-flops in an expensive restaurant,
我都会潸然泪下
I tear up.
是吗
Oh, really?
你不是说过异地恋行不通吗
I thought you said long-distance relationships didn't work.
不会再相隔两地了
Not gonna be long distance anymore.
你洛杉矶的公司怎么办
What about your firm in L.A.?
我们刚在纽约成立了分部
We just opened offices in New York.
都在哪儿啊
Where are they?
就在离我新公寓两个街区的地方
Two blocks from my new apartment I just got.
那你的狗在哪儿
Well, where's your dog?
它舍得它湖人队的赛季联票吗
Doesn't he have season tickets to the Lakers?
他跟杰克·尼科尔森打了一架
He and Jack Nicholson got in a fight.
你之前说过的话你都忘了吗
Well, what about all that stuff you said
你说我们生活不同所处的位置也不同
about us being in different places in our lives?
我想处在你的位置
I want to be in your place.
你还说过你不喜欢
What about that thing you said
我吃面条的方式
about the way I eat noodles?
我正努力接纳
I'm working on that.
麦克斯 自从遇见你那一刻我就为爱痴狂
Max, I've been crazy about you since the moment I met you.
我不能没有你
I don't want to live without you.
-真的吗 -真的
- Oh, really? - Really.
证明给我看
Prove it.
麦克斯·乔治·布莱克
Max George Black...
我爱你
I love you.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
等下 你说什么
Wait, what?
无论是在电影中还是现实中
Caroline can really put you to sleep
卡洛琳都能让你呼呼大睡 对吧
on and off the screen, huh?
来 吃一口
Here, here.
她甚至不喜欢卡洛琳的甜点
Oh, she doesn't even like her desserts.
至少你小睡了一觉 对吧 芭芭拉
Well, at least you got a nap out of it, right, Barbara?
那个睡得口水流一地的人是你吧
You were the one who was drooling pretty hard in there.
不过在看完那部让人打瞌睡的电影
You know what? After seeing that snoozer,
我完全不想让芭芭拉踏入好莱坞了
I don't want Barbara to have any part of Hollywood.
是啊
Yeah.
她可以成为大人物
You know, she can be something important,
比如房产经纪人
like a realtor.
好了
All right,
我用橡皮筋把裙子缝起来
I stitched it up with a rubber band
还在这里系了个渔夫结
and a fisherman's knot right there.
没错 斯蒂芬·西格尔有一条一模一样的裙子
Yeah, Steven Seagal has a dress just like that.
鲍比 我怎么赔得起这条被弄坏的裙子
Bobby, how am I gonna pay for this dress I ruined?
你有一万块吗
Do you have $10,000?
我可以给你四块钱
I can give you $4
然后再帮你多系个渔夫结
and make you another fisherman's knot.
我只想让你知道
I just really want you to know
我对我之前的所作所为感到抱歉
that I am sorry for the way I've been acting.
我懂
Look, I know.
你之前一直为今天焦虑不已
You have been really nervous about today,
也因此引出了我希望已经是你最差的那一面
and it brought out what I hope is the worst in you.
我就顺水推舟说是吧
I'll just say yes.
总而言之 这些外在的东西都不重要
Anyway, none of that superficial stuff matters.
重要的是我爱你
What matters is that I love you,
以及我得赔这裙子一万块
and I owe $10,000 for this dress.
给你提个醒 我看见伦敦 我看见...
Just a heads-up. I see London, I see...
你左半边屁股全露出来了
Your whole left butt cheek is out.
我或许有办法能解决你一万块的赔偿
I may have a solution to your $10,000 problem.
我才不会跟你
I am not going in on
一起合伙加盟小凯撒披萨店
that Little Caesar's franchise with you.
我告诉你 我们到时候做的不仅仅是披萨
We'd be making more than pizza, I'll tell you that.
听着 我现在手里有大量现金
Look, I'm flush with cash now
因为神秘博士的手办停产了
that they've stopped making Dr. Who figurines.
我帮你赔偿这裙子怎么样
How about if I pay for the dress,
你和麦克斯就留在餐厅继续打工抵债
you and Max can pay me back by working at the diner?
阿憨 我愿意
Han, yes.
谢谢你没让我去求你把工作要回来
Thank you for not making me beg for my job back.
你本来会求我吗
You would've begged?
我去走走 打消"升起来"的歪念
Well, I should walk off this boner.
我是说 去带厄尔离开这里
Wait, I mean, go get Earl out of here.
他在向著名大导演
He's pitching his idea for
竭力推销电影"黑人林肯"的想法
The Black Lincoln to Scorsese,
而他对话的那位大导演是一棵植物
and by Scorsese, I mean a plant.
好好考虑一下吧 大导演
Yo, think about it, Marty.
鲍比 我很内疚没有邀请丹妮斯来
Bobby, I felt bad about not inviting Denise,
所以看电影时我给她发短信了
so I texted her during the movie.
希望她够聪明
Hopefully, she'll be smart enough
把服务生的制服换了再过来
to change out of her diner uniform,
她来了 看来还是不够聪明
and there she is, and, no, she wasn't.
通常没这么红
It's not usually this red.
被烧烤架烫红了
I burned it on the grill.
所以今晚最糟糕的部分还没结束
So the worst part of the night's not over.
天啊
Oh, my God.
既复古 又现代
It's retro, it's now,
还有一点番茄酱
it's a little tomato-saucy,
但这造型可以
but it works.
我把意面和肉丸撒自己身上了
I spilled spaghetti and meatballs on myself.
你有女朋友吗
You have a girlfriend?
没有
No.
别担心 我们会找到"三人行"的第三人
Don't worry, we can find a third.
麦克斯发短信给我说
It's from Max. It says,
"速来甜品酒吧 有紧急情况"
"Meet me at the dessert bar. It's an emergency."
她从来不会说某事是紧急情况
She never says something's an emergency.
有一次她来上班时 头上插了一把刀都没说
She came to work with a knife in her head.
麦克斯 你去哪儿了
Max, where did you go?
你错过了一切
You missed everything.
我真的已经尽力了
And as hard as I tried,
可他们就是不愿意再给我一个礼包
they wouldn't give me a second swag bag.
礼包里的瑜伽裤我绝不会跟你分享
And I will not share the Kate Hudson yoga pants.
那个你留着吧 因为我有这个了
You can have them, 'cause I have this!
你居然偷了一个订婚戒指
You stole an engagement ring?
我能出来了吗 里面太臭了
Can I come out now? It smells in there.
天啊 兰迪
Oh, my God, Randy.
麦克斯订婚了你难过吗
Are you upset that Max is engaged?
慢着
Oh, wait!
我懂为什么你告诉她时要我回避了
Now I know why you wanted to tell her without me.
-我回里面臭着吧 -别走
- Back to the smelly room. - No!
我的老天
Oh, my God!
今晚本来我是主角
This night that was totally about me
现在你成了主角 而我一点儿也不嫉妒
is totally about you, and I'm not even jealous!
天啊 你要搬去洛杉矶吗
Oh, my God. Are you moving to L.A.?
喜极而泣要变成悲从中来了
Different kind of tears coming.
不会 我搬来这里
Nope, I'm moving here.
我早就该这么做了
Should've done it a long time ago.
对了 我不冠夫名
I'm keeping my name, by the way.
人们如果叫我兰迪 感觉太奇怪了
It'd be weird for people to call me Randy.
瞧 生活怎么能少了这个呢
See? How can I live without this?
瞧 卡洛琳 你的愿望成真了
See, Caroline? You got your wish.
我们都有伴侣了
We're both with someone.
看来是我的愿望成真了
Looks like I got my wish.
我不会跟你孤独终老
We're not gonna die together.
非常欢迎你跟我们一起终老
You are more than welcome to die with us.
我听说你有个男朋友
So I hear you have a boyfriend.
是啊 他马上就进来
Yeah, he'll be right in.
他帮麦克斯从豪车里把卷心菜沙拉拿出来
He's getting Max's coleslaw out of the limo.
司机说他没有吃
The driver said he didn't eat it,
可他脸上沾满了沙拉酱
but his face is covered in mayonnaise.
鲍比 这位是兰迪
Bobby, this is Randy...
-麦克斯的未婚夫[法语] -什么
- Max's fiance. - What?
如果你不说美语 我就立马跟他分手
Um, I'll break up with him if you don't talk American.
-你看起来好眼熟 -你也是
- You look familiar. - So do you.
你就是那个把
You're that lawyer that
我妈和我姐从真人秀逼走的律师
screwed my mother and sister out of that reality show.
-对 那节目叫... -"搬出去 40岁大宝宝"
- Yeah, it was called... - Move Out, You're 40.
我们不得不解除她们的合约 因为她们是疯子
Yeah, we had to fire them 'cause they're insane.
不好意思 你刚是把
I'm sorry, are you calling
我妈和我姐称为"疯子"吗
my mother and sister insane?
不光是我 整个新泽西州都这么说
Oh, not just me. The state of New Jersey.
真有爱 他们认识彼此
Oh, it's so cute. They know each other.
咱们到外面解决 里面有女士
Let's take this outside. There's ladies here.
只有一个
Well, one.
好主意
That's a good idea.
你这辈子第一个好主意
First one you've ever had.
够了
Okay, that's it.
他妈还诅咒我
His mother put a curse on me.
在那之后你就没找到过好车位了 对吧
Yeah, and you haven't found a good parking space since, have you?
鲍比 别弄坏你的西服 我们赔不起
Bobby, don't ruin your suit. We can't afford it.
天啊 这真是太糟糕了
Oh, my God, this is terrible.
我能再看一眼戒指吗
Can I see the ring again?
我舔过了 不是糖果做的哦
Um, I licked it, and it's not candy.
他们肯定和好了
Aww, they must've made up.
他们抱在一起了
They're hugging.
这不太妙
This is not good.
还有更不妙的事
And more not good,
为了偿还裙子的钱 我们得留在餐厅继续打工
we still have to work at the diner to pay off my dress.
鲍比的妈妈也诅咒我们了吗
Did Bobby's mother put a curse on us too?
我觉得他俩肉搏有点性感 是不是有点怪
Is it weird I think that's a little hot?
再让我看一眼戒指
Let me see the ring again.